http://www.posteranimalhospital.com/site/terms-conditions

×
Search
Website Terms and Conditions
(Last Updated 08/06/2020) Introduction and Acceptance of the Terms and Conditions These website Terms and Conditions are entered into by and between you and PetVet Care Centers (“PetVet”, “we”, “our”, “us”). The following terms and conditions (“Terms and Conditions”) govern your access to and use of our and our medical facilities’, clinics’ and hospitals’ (collectively, “Hospitals”) websites or mobile interfaces or applications (collectively, “Sites”), including any content, functionality, and services offered on or through our Sites, whether as a guest or a registered user. Please read the Terms and Conditions carefully before you start to use the Sites. By using the Sites or by clicking to accept or agree to the Terms and Conditions when this option is made available to you, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by these Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy, found at Privacy Policy, incorporated herein by reference. If you do not want to agree to these Terms and Conditions or the Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the Sites. The Sites is offered and targeted for users in the United States of America who are 13 years of age or older. By using the Sites, you represent and warrant that you are of legal age to form a binding contract with PetVet and meet all of the foregoing eligibility requirements. If you do not meet all of these requirements, you must not access or use the Sites. Changes to the Terms and Conditions We may revise and update these Terms and Conditions from time to time in our sole discretion. All changes are effective immediately when we post them, and apply to all access to and use of the Sites thereafter. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of revised Terms and Conditions means that you accept and agree to the changes. You are expected to check this page each time you access the Sites so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you. Accessing the Sites and Account Security We reserve the right to withdraw or amend the Sites, and any service or material we provide on the Sites, in our sole discretion without notice. We will not be liable if for any reason all or any part of the Sites is unavailable at any time or for any period. From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of, or the entire, Sites to users, including registered users. You are responsible for both:
Making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to the Sites. Ensuring that all persons who access the Sites through your internet connection are aware of these Terms and Conditions and comply with them.
To access the Sites or some of the resources it offers, you may be asked to provide certain registration details or other information. It is a condition of your use of the Sites that all the information you provide on the Sites is correct, current, and complete. You agree that all information you provide to register with the Sites or otherwise, including, but not limited to, through the use of any interactive features on the Sites, is governed by our Privacy Policy at Privacy Policy, and you consent to all actions we take with respect to your information consistent with our Privacy Policy. If you choose, or are provided with, a user name, password, or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any other person or entity. You also acknowledge that your account is personal to you and agree not to provide any other person with access to the Sites or portions of it using your user name, password, or other security information. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized access to or use of your user name or password or any other breach of security. You also agree to ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. You should use particular caution when accessing your account from a public or shared computer so that others are not able to view or record your password or other personal information. We have the right to disable any user name, password, or other identifier, whether chosen by you or provided by us, at any time in our sole discretion for any or no reason, including if, in our opinion, you have violated any provision of these Terms and Conditions. Intellectual Property Rights The Sites and their entire contents, features, and functionality (including but not limited to all information, software, text, displays, images, video, and audio, and the design, selection, and arrangement thereof) are owned by PetVet, its licensors, or other providers of such material and are protected by United States and international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, and other intellectual property or proprietary rights laws. These Terms and Conditions permit you to use the Sites for your personal, non-commercial use only. You must not reproduce, distribute, modify, create derivative works of, publicly display, publicly perform, republish, download, store, or transmit any of the material on our Sites, except as follows:
Your computer may temporarily store copies of such materials in RAM incidental to your accessing and viewing those materials. You may store files that are automatically cached by your Web browser for display enhancement purposes. You may print or download one copy of a reasonable number of pages of the Sites for your own personal, non-commercial use and not for further reproduction, publication, or distribution. If we provide desktop, mobile, or other applications for download, you may download a single copy to your computer or mobile device solely for your own personal, non-commercial use, provided you agree to be bound by our end user license agreement for such applications. If we provide social media features to third-party websites such as Facebook, Linkedin, Instagram, etc. with certain content, you may take such actions as are enabled by such features.
You must not:
Modify copies of any materials from this site. Use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences, or any graphics separately from the accompanying text. Delete or alter any copyright, trademark, or other proprietary rights notices from copies of materials from this site.
You must not access or use for any commercial purposes any part of the Sites or any services or materials available through the Sites. If you print, copy, modify, download, or otherwise use or provide any other person with access to any part of the Sites in breach of the Terms and Conditions, your right to use the Sites will stop immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made. No right, title, or interest in or to the Sites or any content on the Sites is transferred to you, and all rights not expressly granted are reserved by PetVet. Any use of the Sites not expressly permitted by these Terms and Conditions is a breach of these Terms and Conditions and may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws. Trademarks The PetVet Care Centers name and logo on the Sites, and all related or affiliated names, logos, product and service names, designs, and slogans are trademarks of PetVet or its affiliates or licensors. You must not use such marks without the prior written permission of PetVet. All other names, logos, product and service names, designs, and slogans on the Sites are the trademarks of their respective owners. Prohibited Uses You may use the Sites only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms and Conditions. You agree not to use the Sites:
In any way that violates any applicable federal, state, local, or international law or regulation (including, without limitation, any laws regarding the export of data or software to and from the United States of America or other countries). For the purpose of exploiting, harming, or attempting to exploit or harm minors in any way by exposing them to inappropriate content, asking for personally identifiable information, or otherwise.. To transmit, or procure the sending of, any advertising or promotional material, including any "junk mail," "chain letter," "spam," or any other similar solicitation. To impersonate or attempt to impersonate PetVet, a Company employee, another user, or any other person or entity (including, without limitation, by using email addresses associated with any of the foregoing). To engage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits anyone's use or enjoyment of the Sites, or which, as determined by us, may harm PetVet or users of the Sites, or expose them to liability.
Additionally, you agree not to:
Use the Sites in any manner that could disable, overburden, damage, or impair the site or interfere with any other party's use of the Sites, including their ability to engage in real time activities through the Sites. Use any robot, spider, or other automatic device, process, or means to access the Sites for any purpose, including monitoring or copying any of the material on the Sites. Use any manual process to monitor or copy any of the material on the Sites, or for any other purpose not expressly authorized in these Terms and Conditions, without our prior written consent. Use any device, software, or routine that interferes with the proper working of the Sites. Introduce any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, logic bombs, or other material that is malicious or technologically harmful. Attempt to gain unauthorized access to, interfere with, damage, or disrupt any parts of the Sites, the server on which the Sites is stored, or any server, computer, or database connected to the Sites. Attack the Sites via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of-service attack. Otherwise attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Sites.
User Contributions The Sites may contain message boards, chat rooms, personal web pages or profiles, forums, bulletin boards, social media pages, and other interactive features (collectively, “Interactive Services”) that allow users to post, submit, publish, display, or transmit to other users or other persons (hereinafter, “post”) content or materials (collectively, “User Contributions”) on or through the Sites. All User Contributions must comply with the Content Standards set out in these Terms and Conditions. Any User Contribution you post to the site will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary. By providing any User Contribution on the Sites, you grant us and our affiliates and service providers, and each of their and our respective licensees, successors, and assigns the right to use, reproduce, modify, perform, display, distribute, and otherwise disclose to third parties any such material for any purpose. You represent and warrant that:
You own or control all rights in and to the User Contributions and have the right to grant the license granted above to us and our affiliates and service providers, and each of their and our respective licensees, successors, and assigns. All of your User Contributions do and will comply with these Terms and Conditions.
You understand and acknowledge that you are responsible for any User Contributions you submit or contribute, and you, not PetVet, have full responsibility for such content, including its legality, reliability, accuracy, and appropriateness. We are not responsible or liable to any third party for the content or accuracy of any User Contributions posted by you or any other user of the Sites. Monitoring and Enforcement; Termination We have the right to:
Remove or refuse to post any User Contributions for any or no reason in our sole discretion. Take any action with respect to any User Contribution that we deem necessary or appropriate in our sole discretion, including if we believe that such User Contribution violates the Terms and Conditions, including the Content Standards, infringes any intellectual property right or other right of any person or entity, threatens the personal safety of users of the Sites or the public, or could create liability for PetVet. Disclose your identity or other information about you to any third party who claims that material posted by you violates their rights, including their intellectual property rights or their right to privacy. Take appropriate legal action, including without limitation, referral to law enforcement, for any illegal or unauthorized use of the Sites. Terminate or suspend your access to all or part of the Sites for any or no reason, including without limitation, any violation of these Terms and Conditions.
Without limiting the foregoing, we have the right to cooperate fully with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity or other information of anyone posting any materials on or through the Sites. YOU WAIVE AND HOLD HARMLESS PETVET AND ITS AFFILIATES, LICENSEES, AND SERVICE PROVIDERS FROM ANY CLAIMS RESULTING FROM ANY ACTION TAKEN BY PETVET OR ANY OF THE FOREGOING PARTIES DURING, OR TAKEN AS A CONSEQUENCE OF, INVESTIGATIONS BY EITHER PETVET OR SUCH PARTIES OR LAW ENFORCEMENT AUTHORITIES. However, we cannot review all material before it is posted on the Sites, and cannot ensure prompt removal of objectionable material after it has been posted. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any action or inaction regarding transmissions, communications, or content provided by any user or third party. We have no liability or responsibility to anyone for performance or nonperformance of the activities described in this section. Content Standards These content standards apply to any and all User Contributions and use of Interactive Services. User Contributions must in their entirety comply with all applicable federal, state, local, and international laws and regulations. Without limiting the foregoing, User Contributions must not:
Contain any material that is defamatory, obscene, indecent, abusive, offensive, harassing, violent, hateful, inflammatory, or otherwise objectionable. Promote sexually explicit or pornographic material, violence, or discrimination based on race, sex, religion, nationality, disability, sexual orientation, or age. Infringe any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright, or other intellectual property or other rights of any other person. Violate the legal rights (including the rights of publicity and privacy) of others or contain any material that could give rise to any civil or criminal liability under applicable laws or regulations or that otherwise may be in conflict with these Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy at Privacy Policy Be likely to deceive any person. Promote any illegal activity, or advocate, promote, or assist any unlawful act. Cause annoyance, inconvenience, or needless anxiety or be likely to upset, embarrass, alarm, or annoy any other person. Impersonate any person, or misrepresent your identity or affiliation with any person or organization. Involve commercial activities or sales, such as contests, sweepstakes, and other sales promotions, barter, or advertising. Give the impression that they emanate from or are endorsed by us or any other person or entity, if this is not the case.
Reliance on Information Posted The information presented on or through the Sites is made available solely for general information purposes. We do not warrant the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of this information. Any reliance you place on such information is strictly at your own risk. We disclaim all liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such materials by you or any other visitor to the Sites, or by anyone who may be informed of any of its contents. The Sites may include content provided by third parties, including materials provided by other users, bloggers, and third-party licensors, syndicators, aggregators, and/or reporting services. All statements and/or opinions expressed in these materials, and all articles and responses to questions and other content, other than the content provided by PetVet, are solely the opinions and the responsibility of the person or entity providing those materials. These materials do not necessarily reflect the opinion of PetVet. We are not responsible, or liable to you or any third party, for the content or accuracy of any materials provided by any third parties. IF YOU SUSPECT YOUR PET REQUIRES MEDICAL ATTENTION, PLEASE SEEK APPROPRIATE VETERINARY MEDICAL CARE IMMEDIATELY BY CALLING A VETERINARY MEDICAL PROFESSIONAL INSTEAD OF RELYING ON ANY INFORMATION PRESENTED ON OR THROUGH THE SITES. IN ADDITION, PLEASE DO NOT DISREGARD ANY OF YOUR VETERINARY CARE PROFESSIONAL’S ADVICE OR DELAY SEEKING SUCH ADVICE BECAUSE OF ANY INFORMATION PRESENTED ON OR THROUGH OR OTHERWISE RELATED TO THE SITES. Changes to the Sites We may update the content on the Sites from time to time, but its content is not necessarily complete or up-to-date. Any of the material on the Sites may be out of date at any given time, and we are under no obligation to update such material. Information About You and Your Visits to the Sites All information we collect on the Sites is subject to our Privacy Policy at Privacy Policy. By using the Sites, you consent to all actions taken by us with respect to your information in compliance with the Privacy Policy. Linking to the Sites and Social Media Features You may link to our homepage, provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal and does not damage our reputation or take advantage of it, but you must not establish a link in such a way as to suggest any form of association, approval, or endorsement on our part without our express consent. The Sites may provide certain social media features that enable you to:
Link from your own or certain third-party websites to certain content on the Sites. Send emails or other communications with certain content, or links to certain content, on the Sites. Cause limited portions of content on the Sites to be displayed or appear to be displayed on your own or certain third-party websites.
You may use these features solely as they are provided by us and otherwise in accordance with any additional terms and conditions we provide with respect to such features. Subject to the foregoing, you must not:
Establish a link from any website that is not owned by you. Cause the Sites or portions of it to be displayed on, or appear to be displayed by, any other site, for example, framing, deep linking, or in-line linking. Link to any part of the Sites other than the homepage. Otherwise take any action with respect to the materials on the Sites that is inconsistent with any other provision of these Terms and Conditions.
The Sites from which you are linking, or on which you make certain content accessible, must comply in all respects with the Content Standards set out in these Terms and Conditions. You agree to cooperate with us in causing any unauthorized framing or linking immediately to stop. We reserve the right to withdraw linking permission without notice. We may disable all or any social media features and any links at any time without notice in our discretion. Links from the Sites If the Sites contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your convenience only. This includes links contained in advertisements, including banner advertisements and sponsored links. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. If you decide to access any of the third-party websites linked to the Sites, you do so entirely at your own risk and subject to the terms and conditions of use for such websites. Geographic Restrictions The owner of the Sites is based in the United States. We provide the Sites for use only by persons located in the United States. We make no claims that the Sites or any of its content is accessible or appropriate outside of the United States. Access to the Sites may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Sites from outside the United States, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws. Disclaimer of Warranties You understand that we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant that files available for downloading from the internet or the Sites will be free of viruses or other destructive code. You are responsible for implementing sufficient procedures and checkpoints to satisfy your particular requirements for anti-virus protection and accuracy of data input and output, and for maintaining a means external to our site for any reconstruction of any lost data. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PROVIDED BY LAW, WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY A DISTRIBUTED DENIAL-OF-SERVICE ATTACK, VIRUSES, OR OTHER TECHNOLOGICALLY HARMFUL MATERIAL THAT MAY INFECT YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT, COMPUTER PROGRAMS, DATA, OR OTHER PROPRIETARY MATERIAL DUE TO YOUR USE OF THE SITES OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITES OR TO YOUR DOWNLOADING OF ANY MATERIAL POSTED ON IT, OR ON ANY WEBSITE LINKED TO IT. YOUR USE OF THE SITES, ITS CONTENT, AND ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITES IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE SITES, ITS CONTENT, AND ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. NEITHER PETVET NOR ANY PERSON ASSOCIATED WITH PETVET MAKES ANY WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION WITH RESPECT TO THE COMPLETENESS, SECURITY, RELIABILITY, QUALITY, ACCURACY, OR AVAILABILITY OF THE SITES. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, NEITHER PETVET NOR ANYONE ASSOCIATED WITH PETVET REPRESENTS OR WARRANTS THAT THE SITES, ITS CONTENT, OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITES WILL BE ACCURATE, RELIABLE, ERROR-FREE, OR UNINTERRUPTED, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, THAT OUR SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, OR THAT THE SITES OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITES WILL OTHERWISE MEET YOUR NEEDS OR EXPECTATIONS.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PROVIDED BY LAW, PETVET HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY, OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, AND FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THE FOREGOING DOES NOT AFFECT ANY WARRANTIES THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW. Limitation on Liability TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PROVIDED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL PETVET, ITS AFFILIATES, OR THEIR LICENSORS, SERVICE PROVIDERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, OFFICERS, OR DIRECTORS BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE, OR INABILITY TO USE, THE SITES, ANY WEBSITES LINKED TO IT, ANY CONTENT ON THE SITES OR SUCH OTHER WEBSITES, INCLUDING ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PERSONAL INJURY, PAIN AND SUFFERING, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, LOSS OF REVENUE, LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR ANTICIPATED SAVINGS, LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF GOODWILL, LOSS OF DATA, AND WHETHER CAUSED BY TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), BREACH OF CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF FORESEEABLE. THE FOREGOING DOES NOT AFFECT ANY LIABILITY THAT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW. Indemnification You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless PetVet, its affiliates, licensors, and service providers, and its and their respective officers, directors, employees, contractors, agents, licensors, suppliers, successors, and assigns from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, judgments, awards, losses, costs, expenses, or fees (including reasonable attorneys' fees) arising out of or relating to your violation of these Terms and Conditions or your use of the Sites, including, but not limited to, your User Contributions, any use of the Sites’s content, services, and products other than as expressly authorized in these Terms and Conditions, or your use of any information obtained from the Sites. Governing Law and Jurisdiction All matters relating to the Sites and these Terms and Conditions, and any dispute or claim arising therefrom or related thereto (in each case, including non-contractual disputes or claims), shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of Connecticut without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law provision or rule (whether of the State of Connecticut or any other jurisdiction). Any legal suit, action, or proceeding arising out of, or related to, these Terms and Conditions or the Sites shall be instituted exclusively in the federal courts of the United States or the courts of the State of Connecticut although we retain the right to bring any suit, action, or proceeding against you for breach of these Terms and Conditions in your country of residence or any other relevant country. You waive any and all objections to the exercise of jurisdiction over you by such courts and to venue in such courts. Limitation on Time to File Claims ANY CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OR THE SITES MUST BE COMMENCED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES; OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM IS PERMANENTLY BARRED. Waiver and Severability No waiver by PetVet of any term or condition set out in these Terms and Conditions shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or a waiver of any other term or condition, and any failure of PetVet to assert a right or provision under these Terms and Conditions shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of these Terms and Conditions is held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, illegal, or unenforceable for any reason, such provision shall be eliminated or limited to the minimum extent such that the remaining provisions of the Terms and Conditions will continue in full force and effect. Entire Agreement The Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy constitute the sole and entire agreement between you and PetVet regarding the Sites and supersede all prior and contemporaneous understandings, agreements, representations, and warranties, both written and oral, regarding the Sites. Intellectual Property Infringement All notices of copyright, trademark or other intellectual property infringement claims relating to any content presented on or through the Sites should be sent to our Legal Department at legal@petvetcarecenters.com. Please note that any notice of claimed infringement should be made in writing and include all of the following: (a) a physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the intellectual property interest that is allegedly infringed; (b) a description of such protected work(s) and an identification of what material in such work(s) is claimed to be infringed; (c) a description of the exact name of the infringing work and the location of the infringing work on the Sites; (d) contact information, such as your physical address, telephone number and e-mail address; (e) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the use of the material identified in the manner complained of is not authorized by the intellectual property owner, its agent, or the law; (f) a statement by you that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on the intellectual property owner’s behalf.
New Patients Welcome
Poster Veterinary Associates has been providing comprehensive veterinary care for your cherished pets in Westport since 1993.
Copyright © 2020 Poster Veterinary Associates | All Rights Reserved. Part of the PetVet Care Centers Network. Managed with Tymbrel
203-259-3647
